Devki Zunzurwad

dzunzurwad@gmail.com| +917057280029

Devki zunzurwad-Linkedin

SUMMARY

1+ year of working experience in different domain using data science skills. Enthusiast learner of deep leaning, machine learning and python along with data science techniques like CNN & Vision algorithms, finding simple solutions by using ML algorithms to complex in deep learning field usecases.

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF PUNE

B.E. in Computer Engineering Jul 2017 – Jul 2021 | Pune, MH CGPA – 7.62/10

COURSEWORK

UNDERGRADUATE

Data Structures and Algorithms Theoretical Computer Science Operating System Deep Learning Machine Learning Artificial Intelligence, Soft Computing

SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

Python • C • C++, Java

OPERATING SYSTEMS

Windows

Linux

TOOLS AND LIBRARIES

Pandas • NumPy • Scikit-learn, OpenCV, Tensorflow, Pytorch, JAX, Docker.

SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT

HTML • CSS • Bootstrap •SQL •MongoDB •Git, GitHub

CERTIFICATIONS

Web Developer Intern certificate

Develop web application using HTML, CSS and JavaScript

Full Stack Data Science Boot Camp**
iNeuron.ai

EXPERIENCE

HUDL INDIA PVT. LTD. | DATA ANALYST JUNE 2021-JUNE2022

• Extracting the data, cleaning the data, Data preparing for model training and setting up end to end data & model development pipeline.

UPTRICKS SERVICES | WEB DEVELOPER INTERN JAN 2021-APRIL 2021

- Design and implement web application using HTML, CSS, XHTML, Bootstrap and WordPress.
- Develop demo website for client DMOS using responsive web design.
- Develop web application front-end and backend components.

PROJECTS

TRAFFIC VEHICLE DETECTION

- In this Project we considered video as an input, and frames are considered for processing.
- Deep learning methods are used in detection of object and its tracking algorithm
- Tools- Deep learning, Image Processing, TensorFlow, OpenCV.

FOOTBALL ANALYTICS WITH OBJECT DETECTION

- To predict the score of matches by observing team players we used techniques like computer vision, Image Processing.
- Use frameworks like Object Tracking, Object Detection.
- **Tools** Computer vision, PyTorch, OpenCV.

STOCK PRICE PREDICTION AND DETECTION

- Used daily stock price data, collected at five minutes interval of time of a very wellknown company that is listed in Stock Exchange.
- Granular data is aggregated into three slots in a day and the aggregated data is used for building and training forecasting models.
- Tools- Pandas, NumPy, Scikit-Learn, Matplotlib.